{
    "id": "d036a3f8898b4f3a9c282e8089cb0160",
    "title": "Such And So | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is .......................... a lovely woman.",
            "description": "We use such before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d3bb900c150e425a860254e6b4bdb30b"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was ............................. a lot of commotion that I could not understand anything.",
            "description": "We use such before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a99cf73cc45847079abd1bd08be0576d"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is .............................. much work to do.",
            "description": "We use so before much and many.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b5fd7d1cbca74cc986d5a73586ee6cde"
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ............................... many applicants and ............................. few vacancies.",
            "description": "We use so before many and few.",
            "answers": [
                "so, so",
                "so, such",
                "such, so",
                "such, such"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "68130d6f76324947a0924b6b918f598f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had never seen ............................... much food in my life.",
            "description": "We use so before such.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bd72729193b445898a6c907bcd41aaee"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is .............................. patient with her students.",
            "description": "We use so before adjectives and adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ca31a7aac200467c9678afef638bc1f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am surprised that you have got ................................. patience.",
            "description": "We use such before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "642011b848e54c02a1c10d804f621a7b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am surprised that you have got ............................ much strength.",
            "description": "We use so before much.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "61094350644e4d559f7f8b2fa5a83266"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are ................................ sweet baby.",
            "description": "Such comes before a/an.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "a such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "66e3f96e0c60416b922c087eed0718ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ................................. an unforgettable experience.",
            "description": "We use such before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a4c86a89b6c543659cf34e63cdf48397"
        },
        {
            "question": "The watch was ............................... expensive that I didn't buy it.",
            "description": "We use so before a that-clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fe1268c4ee7a433288dc958a3ac54ff7"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is .............................. warm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d204b04b1162474c8fb6e9c4b466418e"
        }
    ]
}